Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of Senior V.P. for; Records ua500
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Program Proposal and Review Records, 1951-2019; 6; 52.66 cubic ft.
  - Computer Science and Applied Mathematics, 1979-1981 (Box 44 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Planning and Policy Analysis, Advanced Certificate, ca. 1978-1981 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, Ph.D., ca. 1978-1984 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - School of Business, 1978-1982 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Disability Determinations, 1978-1983 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Reading, Ed.D., 1978-1983; ca. 1992-1994 (Box 41 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Regional Planning, M.R.P., 1978-1986 (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Communication, 1978-1987 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Art, 1978-1989 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Counseling Psychology, 1978-1991 (Box 43 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Atmospheric Science, 1978 (Box 7 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Anthropology, Ph.D., 1978 (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Atmospheric Science, 1978 (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, ca. 1978 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, Ph.D., 1978 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Chemistry, Ph.D., 1978 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, D.A., 1978 (Box 16 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Hispanic and Italian Studies, ca. 1978 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Rhetoric and Communication, Ph.D., 1978 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Certificate of Advanced Criminal Justice Study, 1978 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Local History, Ph.D., 1978 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Professional Studies, M.S., 1979 (Box 53 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Master of Fine Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 49 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Theatre, M.F.A., 1979-1980 (Box 49 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Classics, M.A., 1979-1981 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Studio Art, M.F.A., 1979-1981 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Spanish, Ph.D., ca. 1979-1981 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Asian Studies, 1979-1981 (Box 19 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Russian and East European Studies, 1979-1981 (Box 41 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Curriculum and Instruction, Ed.D., 1979-1982 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Policy and Administration, M.A., Joint SUNY/CUNY degree, ca. 1979-1983 (Box 30 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, Ph.D., 1979-1984 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Information Science, 1979-1990 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Classics, 1979 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - School Media Specialist, Certification, 1979 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Spanish, Ph.D., 1979 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, ca. 1979; 1990 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biological Sciences, ca. 1979 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Linguistics, M.A., ca. 1979 (Box 36 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, Ph.D., ca. 1979 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Discourse Theory - Reading and Writing, 1980 (Box 53 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Chinese Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 22 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Division of Laboratories, Ph.D., 1980-1981 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, Ph.D., ca. 1980-1981; 1990-1992 (Box 31 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Anthropology, 1980-1981 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geography, 1980-1981 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1980-1981 (Box 53 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Court Systems Management, Certificate, ca. 1980-1983 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geography, 1980-1984 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geography, ca. 1980-1984 (Box 31 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Combined Bachelor's/Master's and Dual-Master's Programs, ca. 1980-1986 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Sociology, Ph.D., ca. 1980s; 1977 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - School of Public Health Sciences, ca. 1980s (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Environmental Health and Toxicology, ca. 1980s (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Pathobiology, ca. 1980s (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Epidemiology, ca. 1980s (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1980s (Box 7 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1980s (Box 7 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Program Review Committee, ca. 1980s (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - State Education Department Correspondence, ca. 1980s (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Letters of Intent - Other Institutions, ca. 1980s (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Sociology, ca. 1980s (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Urban Policy, Certificate, ca. 1980s (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biopsychology, Ph.D., ca. 1980s (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Program Review Documents, ca. 1980s (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Humanistic Studies, D.A., ca. 1980s (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biological Sciences, ca. 1980s (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, M.A., ca. 1980s (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Undergraduate Studies Material, ca. 1980s (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biometry and Statistics, M.S., ca. 1980s (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, ca. 1980s (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Program in Administration, ca. 1980s (Box 22 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Psychology, ca. 1980s (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Combined Degree Programs, ca. 1980s (Box 38 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Letters of Intent - Other Institutions, ca. 1980s (Box 52 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - New Paltz and Albany Joint MA Sociology and MSW, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Urban Education, Graduate Certificate, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Mathematics, Ph.D., 1980 (Box 11 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Mathematics, Ph.D., 1980 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Literacy, Ph.D., ca. 1980 (Box 47 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Education Proposals - Social Sciences, ca. 1981-1982 (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - University at Albany and Albany Law School Joint B.S./ J.D., 1981-1982; 1988-1989 (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Center for Laboratories and Research, 1981-1982 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Court Systems Management, 1981-1982 (Box 32 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Theatre, 1981-1982 (Box 42 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Physics, 1981-1983 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, Ph.D., 1981-1983 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - History, 1981-1983 (Box 54 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Atmospheric Science, ca. 1981-1984 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Environmental Health and Toxicology, M.S., Ph.D., ca. 1981-1985 (Box 27 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biology, Ph.D., ca. 1981-1986 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Russian, M.A., ca. 1981 (Box 5 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Education Proposals - Social Sciences, ca. 1981 (Box 16 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Education Proposals - Literature and the Fine Arts, ca. 1981 (Box 16 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Education Proposals - Literature and the Fine Arts, ca. 1981 (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Education Proposals - Natural Sciences, ca. 1981 (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Theatre, 1982 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Classics, ca. 1982 (Box 53 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - History, ca. 1982-1983 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geological Sciences, ca. 1982-1983 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Advanced Public Management, Certificate, 1982-1983 (Box 25 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Theatre, 1982-1983 (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Pathobiology, M.S., Ph.D., ca. 1982-1983 (Box 27 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Organizational Analysis, Ph.D., 1982-1983 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Humanistic Studies, D.A., 1982-1984 (Box 31 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Committee on Program Review, ca. 1982-1984 (Box 34 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Music, 1982-1984 (Box 54 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Organizational Studies, Ph.D., 1982-1985 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biology, Ph.D., ca. 1982-1988 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Epidemiology, M.S., 1982-1988 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Business Education, 1982-1988 (Box 43 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Russian Translation, Certificate, 1982 (Box 5 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geological Sciences, 1982 (Box 6 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Regulatory Economics, Certificate, ca. 1982 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Physics, 1982 (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public History, Certificate, ca. 1982 (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, Ph.D., 1982 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Physics, 1982 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - General Education Proposals - Writing Intensive Courses, ca. 1982 (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Court Systems Management, Certificate, ca. 1982 (Box 23 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Physics, ca. 1982 (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biomedical Sciences, Ph.D., ca. 1982 (Box 27 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biological Sciences, 1982 (Box 33 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Social Welfare, 1982 (Box 42 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geological Sciences, 1982 (Box 44 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, Advanced Certificate, ca. 1983-1984 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Psychology, Ph.D.s, 1983-1989 (Box 43 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Accreditation Correspondence, ca. 1983-1990 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Teacher Education, 1983-1991 (Box 42 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French, 1983 (Box 7 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French, B.A., M.A., 1983 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Theatre, ca. 1983 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Laboratory Medicine, M.S., Ph.D., ca. 1983 (Box 27 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Counseling, 1982 (Box 43 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Music, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Psychology, Ph.D.s, ca. 1984-1990 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, ca. 1984-1992 (Box 6 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biostatistics, M.S., 1984 (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Music, 1984 (Box 7 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Music, B.A., 1984 (Box 9 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Music, B.A., 1984 (Box 22 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Regional Planning, M.R.P., ca. 1985-1986 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Afro-American Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Institute for the Study of Information Science, ca. 1985-1989 (Box 38 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Letters of Intent - Other Institutions, 1985-1989 (Box 53 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Educational Theory and Practice, 1985-1990 (Box 44 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Letters of Intent, ca. 1985-2002 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Communication, 1985 (Box 6 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, B.S., 1985 (Box 11 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Demography, Certificate, 1985 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Organizational Studies, Ph.D., 1985 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Communication, 1985 (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Political Science, ca. 1986-1987 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Administration, Ph.D., ca. 1986-1988 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Sector Management, Certificate, 1986-1988 (Box 30 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, M.A., 1986-1988 (Box 36 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Curriculum Development and Instructional Technology, M.S., 1986-1988 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Educational Administration and Policy Studies, ca. 1986-1988 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Health, M.P.H., Dr.P.H., 1986-1995 (Box 27 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biomedical Sciences, Ph.D., ca. 1986-1998 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, B.A., M.A., 1986 (Box 9 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, B.A., M.A., 1986 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Accounting, M.S., 1986 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Policy, 1986 (Box 30 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Women and Public Policy, Certificate, 1986 (Box 30 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 1987-1988 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Educational Administration and Policy Studies, ca. 1987-1988 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Committee on Curriculum and Instruction, Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Criminal Justice, 1987-1989 (Box 23 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Art, ca. 1987-1989 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Information Science, Ph.D., 1987-1990 (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, B.S. - Computer Sciences Accreditation Board, ca. 1987-1992 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, Ph.D., ca. 1987-1993 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Epidemiology, Ph.D., 1987-1994 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Psychology, Ph.D.s, ca. 1987-2001 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Social-Personality Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1987 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Industrial-Organizational Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1987 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geographic Information Systems and Spatial Analysis, Certificate, ca. 1987 (Box 10 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Geographic Information Systems and Spatial Analysis, Certificate, 1987 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Political Science, 1987 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Latin American and Caribbean Studies, 1987 (Box 31 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Counseling Psychology, ca. 1987 (Box 45 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Art, ca. 1988-1989 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Women's Studies, B.A., 1988-1989 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Anthropology, 1988-1989 (Box 18 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Neuroscience, M.S., Ph.D., ca. 1988-1989 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1988-1990 (Box 6 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Industrial/Organizational Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1988-1990 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, ca. 1988-1991 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Industrial/Organizational Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1988-1991 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, Ph.D., 1988-1991 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - German, 1988-1991 (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, ca. 1988-1992 (Box 5 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biometry and Statistics, Ph.D., 1988-1992 (Box 15 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Information Science, Ph.D., 1988-1998 (Box 35 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Statistics, M.S., 1988 (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Communication, M.A., 1988 (Box 7 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Applied Physics, B.S., 1988 (Box 11 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Affairs, 1988 (Box 12 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Information Science, Ph.D., 1988 (Box 41 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Health, M.P.H., 1989-1990 (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - German, ca. 1989-1990 (Box 6 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English Ph.D., 1989-1990 (Box 18 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Mathematics, 1989-1990 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - History, Ph.D., ca. 1989-1991 (Box 20 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Health Policy and Management, M.S., 1989-1991 (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Health Policy and Management, M.S., 1989-1991 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French Studies, Ph.D., ca. 1989-1991 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, 1989-1991 (Box 33 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Industrial/Organizational Psychology, Ph.D., 1989-1991 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, Ph.D., 1989-1992 (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French Studies, Ph.D., ca. 1989-1998 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy Ph.D., ca. 1989-2001 (Box 36 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Middle States Assessment and Accreditation, ca. 1989-2003 (Box 40 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Health, Dr.P.H., 1989 (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, Ph.D., 1989 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, Ph.D., 1989 (Box 8 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Health, Dr.P.H., 1989 (Box 26 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Biometry and Statistics, M.S., 1989 (Box 27 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Information Science, M.S., Ph.D., 1983 (Box 38 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Interdisciplinary Majors - Religious Studies, Information Science, ca. 1989 (Box 48 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Curriculum and Instruction, Ph.D., ca. 1990 (Box 52 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Regional Planning, M.R.P., ca. 1990-1991 (Box 11 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, ca. 1990-1991 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Educational Psychology and Statistics, Ph.D., 1990-1991 (Box 17 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, 1990-1991 (Box 33 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French Studies, Ph.D., ca. 1990-1991 (Box 35 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Rehabilitation Counselor Education Program, 1990-1991 (Box 41 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, Ph.D., 1990-1993 (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, Ph.D., ca. 1990-1996 (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - French Studies, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Anthropology, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Criminal Justice, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - History, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Organizational Studies, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Political Science, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Public Administration and Policy, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Sociology, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Social Welfare, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Psychology, ca. 1990s (Box 2 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Information Science, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Educational Psychology and Statistics, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Cognitive Psychology, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Computer Science, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Health Policy and Management, M.S., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Environmental and Occupational Health, M.S., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - History, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 3 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - History, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 4 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Letters of Intent, ca. 1990s (Box 5 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Doctoral Program Review Materials, ca. 1990s (Box 21 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - English, Ph.D., ca. 1990s (Box 35 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - State Postsecondary Review Entities (SPREs), ca. 1990s (Box 37 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Mathematics and Statistics, 1990 (Box 6 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Reading, Ph.D., ca. 1990 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Teaching, Certificate, ca. 1990 (Box 13 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Business Administration, 1990 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - School of Information Science and Policy, 1990 (Box 14 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Economics, 1990 (Box 18 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Preventive Medicine, Residency, ca. 1990 (Box 28 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Philosophy, Ph.D., 1990 (Box 29 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))
  - Mathematics, 1990 (Box 31 (6-Program Proposal and Review Records))